你想象一下这个社区
So imagine this neighborhood
重建辉煌  兄弟
is restored to glory, dawg.
就想象这个街区
Imagine this block right here.
面具已经是过去式了  人潮涌动
Masks are just a bad memory. Imagine the crowds,
餐厅火爆  酒吧爆满
the dope restaurants, the powerful bars--
我还能想象到老鼠
I'm imagining the rats too.
想象一下别打断我的感觉
Imagine not interrupting me.
想象现金涌入你的口袋
And imagine the cash flow in your pocket.
凯文  为什么  因为我是酒保吗
Ah, Kev, what? Because I'm the bartender?
不  因为整个楼是你的  鲁塞克
No, 'cause you own the building, Ruz, damn.
我有门路  懂吗
I got an "In," okay?
几个特别聪明的商业人士  他们欠我人情
A couple smart as hell business guys, they owe me a favor.
只要区域安全了
They said as soon as the zone clears,
-我们就能让这里重焕生机  -说不好  兄弟
- we can turn this thing around. - I don't know, buddy.
我觉得要等到这个社区发展起来
I think we're gonna be dead and buried
咱俩估计早就老了
by the time this neighborhood comes up.
哥们  你想想西圈
Come on, bro. Think about the West Loop.
要是我们当时先想到了西圈
I mean, we'd be rolling in cash right now
现在早就已经盆满钵满了
if we would've thought about the West Loop.
我知道这个街区以前什么样  兄弟
I just know what this place used to be, dawg,
我觉得我们能让它恢复昔日荣光
and I feel like we could bring it back.
我觉得我一直在想
I feel like I'm wondering about the beer
你答应我的啤酒  这是在干什么
that you promised me. What's happening here?
我感觉被你骗了  我的啤酒呢
I feel a little hoodwinked. I want my beer, man.
别这样  肯定请你喝
Come on, bro. I got you.
芝加哥各巡逻队
Units on the Citywide.
收到几通报警电话说有枪声
We're getting multiple calls of shots fired.
34大道和威尔森路  报警者称
34th and Wilson. Caller states
枪声来自一家五金店
the shots are coming from inside a hardware store.
5021D  总部  请重复地址
5021 David. Squad, repeat that address.
34大道和威尔森路  东南侧
34th and Wilson. Southeast corner.
5021D  总部  我们在五街区远的地方
5021 David. Squad, we're five blocks away.
-怎么  你知道那地方吗  -我知道店主
- What? You know the place? - No, the owner.
收到  这就显示你们出警
Copy that. We'll show you en route.
罗伊五金店  油漆及日用品
女士  请您离这里远一些  谢谢
Ma'am, can you move on down the way, please?
准备好了吗
You ready?
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy!
芝加哥警署  有人在吗
Chicago PD. Anybody in here?
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy...
总部  请派救护车来  有人受伤
Squad, roll an ambo. We got one down.
胸部遭到枪伤  男性  60多岁
GSW to the chest. Male. 60s.
没关系  我在呢
It's okay. It's okay. I got you.
我不能丢下他  你先去
I can't leave him. Go. Go.
你要坚持住  罗伊先生  我陪着你
Don't go anywhere, Mr. Roy. I got you.
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
我在呢  坚持住  老哥
I got you. Just hold on, OG.
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
好吗  要不克莱尔会把咱俩都杀了
All right? Or Mama Claire will kill us both.
坚持住  罗伊先生
Come on, Mr. Roy.
坚持住  看着我  看着我
Come on. Look at me. Look at me.
翻译    青椒   nemonini    哈里不是波特
看着我
Look at me.
翻译    苏葵*4
-鲁塞克  你还好吗  -我没事
- Ruz, you good? - Yeah.
校对    苏葵
我是5021I  有人向警察开枪
5021 Ida, shots fired at the police.
歹徒从后门逃跑了
Offender's fleeing out the back door.
-黑色上衣  蓝色裤子  -收到
- Black jacket, blue jeans. - Copy that.
时间轴    Jenny   西查   chance-coco
支援已经在路上
Backup en route.
后期    8T
总监    苏葵
站住  警察
Stop! Police!
警察  站住
Police! Freeze!
芝加哥警署
第八季第九集
你认识他吗
You knew him?
恩格尔伍德是我刚开始工作的地方
You know, Englewood was my first beat.
我和罗伊先生一见如故
Me and Mr. Roy hit it off from the jump.
他是个大好人  警长
He was real good people, Sarge.
他在乎家人  在乎邻里
He cared about his family, the community.
好
Okay.
情况如何
All right, what are we thinking?
-持枪抢劫吗  -收银机的钱都没了
- Armed robbery? - The register was cleared out,
但是钱包还在他身上
but his wallet was still on him.
法医说罗伊的面部
The M.E. said there was fresh contusions
有新鲜的擦伤痕迹
and abrasion on Roy's face.
他被人施暴后近距离射杀
He was beaten and shot at close range.
好  绝对是私人恩怨
Oh, yeah. This was personal.
我们对于歹徒所知多少
All right, what do we know about the offender?
我没太看清
I didn't get a good look at all.
170到175
5'10". 170.
戴了口罩  鲁塞克说他跑得很快
Masked up. Ruzek said he was fast as hell.
监控有吗
Surveillance?
里面没有监控  警长
No security cameras inside, Sarge.
我几年前就劝他装上
I told him to put those things in years ago.
他不喜欢监控给人的感觉
He didn't like the message they sent.
我们为他主持公道吧
Well, let's get him the justice he deserves.
好好查街头监控  跟目击证人聊聊
Okay, check PODs, talk to witnesses.
-多在街上查一查  -不  不
- Hit the streets hard. - No! No! No!
-不要  -行动
- No! No! - All right, let's go.
那是罗伊先生的妻子  我去跟她聊聊
Mr. Roy's wife. I'ma talk to her.
好  去吧
Yeah. Okay.
-凯文  我的罗伊...  -克莱尔女士
- Kev! Kevin, is my Roy... - Ms. Claire.
警长
Sergeant?
我听说了谋杀案的事  有线索吗
I heard about the murder. Any leads?
正在调查  还不能汇报
Chasing a few. Nothing to report yet.
你从塔里过来挺远的
You're kind of far from the Tower.
看来不是随机抽查
I gather this isn't a random inspection.
不是
It's not.
我想跟你聊聊安德烈·库珀的事
I want to talk about Andre Cooper.
就是他的搭档枪杀了...
You know, the young man whose partner shot and killed--
我知道他是谁
Yeah, I know who he is.
那孩子的日子不好过
The kid's having a rough time.
黑人警察恨他做得不够多
Black cops are shunning him for not doing more.
白人警察又说他
The white cops are calling him out
不支持自己的搭档
for not backing up his partner.
库珀是他们那届的毕业优等生代表
Cooper was the valedictorian of his academy class.
我不希望他的事业还没开始就结束
I don't want his career to end before it starts.
我理解
Yeah. I get that.
但是我不懂你希望我做什么
Just don't know what you want me to do here.
让他去情报组
Bring him into Intelligence.
就当我欠你一个人情  汉克
I would think of it as a personal favor, Hank.
我的人都是我亲手挑选的
My team's handpicked by me.
你知道我可以直接把他派到情报组  对吧
You realize I could just assign him to Intelligence, right?
知道
I do.
但你没有这么做
But you didn't.
他现在就在我的车里坐着呢
Well, he's sitting in my SUV right now.
至少你可以跟他做个自我介绍
Least you could do is introduce yourself.
我不清楚副警司是怎么和你说的
Look, I don't know what the deputy super told you,
但情报组非常特别
but Intelligence is pretty unique.
整个团队只有6到7个警员
I mean, there's only six or seven cops in the whole unit.
没什么空缺
There's just not a lot of open positions.
我能直说吗  长官
Can I be blunt, sir?
这不是我的主意
This wasn't my idea.
她让我上车  坐车走一趟
She told me to jump in the car and take a ride.
如果她让你为难了
So if she put you in a awkward position,
我表示道歉
I apologize.
虽然能在情报组工作
And as much as it would be an honor
是莫大的荣幸
to work in Intelligence,
我不需要特别关照
I don't want any special favors.
那你想要什么呢
What do you want?
参与到行动里
To be in the game.
在一线工作
In the middle of it.
如果你想要带来改变  做些好事
If you want to make a difference, do some good,
你得在街上
you gotta be on the streets,
在邻里之中  与大家交谈
in the community, talking to people.
很高兴和你聊聊  安德烈
It was nice talking to you, Andre.
别怪我多嘴  警长
For what it's worth, Sergeant,
我去查过街对面的披萨店
I checked that pizza joint across the street.
-嗯  -看见有个家伙
- Okay. - Saw a guy duck back in
一看见巡警过来就缩回去了
when he saw patrol coming.
餐馆很快就从营业变成关门状态了
Place went from open to closed real quick.
他长什么样
What did he look like?
黑人  40来岁
Black. 40s.
有1米95  偏瘦
6'5". Slender build.
穿着蓝色牛仔裤  棕色劳保鞋
Had on blue jeans, brown steel-toe boots,
一件珍藏版乔丹的公牛队服
a vintage Bulls Jordan jacket.
珍藏版
Vintage?
红色皮袖的  他们已经不再生产了
The red leather sleeves. They don't make those anymore.
谢谢你提供的情报
Appreciate the heads-up.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
目击者
Witness?
没有  有个大人唠叨停车的限制
No. Grown man bitching about parking restrictions.
我需要你叫上凯文
Listen, I want you to grab Kevin.
去查查角上那家披萨店
Check out that pizza joint on the corner.
我想也许老板知道点什么
I think the owner might know something.
好
All right.
海耶斯披萨
抱歉  我们关门了
Sorry, we're closed.
我不是来吃披萨饼的  鲍勃
I'm not here for the pie, Bob.
我想聊聊街对面的凶杀案
I want to talk to you about the homicide across the street.
罗伊去世太可惜了
It's a damn shame about Roy.
什么世道
What a world.
-你们抓到那家伙了吗  -还没有  先生
- You catch the guy? - No, sir, not yet.
我们正是为了这个来的
That's exactly why we're here.
在枪响之前或之后你看到什么可疑的情况吗
Did you see anything suspicious before or after the gunshots?
没有  我在后面
No, I was in the back.
我们看见你门上有黑帮的记号
We noticed gang tags on your doors.
你有麻烦吗  他们一直在骚扰你吗
That a problem for you? They've been harassing you?
-他们是好顾客  -真的
- They're good customers. - Really?
因为三个月前  你还报过警
Because three months ago, you filed a police report that
说两个黑社会对你的一个店员动了手
said two gangbangers roughed up one of your employees
还砸碎了窗户玻璃
and smashed out windows.
那只是...只是误会
That was just... just a misunderstanding.
鲍勃  罗伊先生是我的好朋友
Bob, Mr. Roy was a good friend to me,
如果你知道什么  你得现在就告诉我
so if you know anything, you need to tell me now
因为不抓住凶手我不会罢休
because I'm not going to sleep until I find his killer.
我帮不了你  很抱歉
I can't help you. I'm sorry.
我可不是英雄  兄弟
I ain't no hero, brother.
我有老婆和两个小孩
I got a wife and two little kids.
你想起什么  给我打电话
You think of anything, call me.
我的线人告诉我这一带
My CI told me that Quincy Barrett
是昆西·巴雷特管的  他的案底长着呢
runs that neighborhood. He's got a strong sheet.
凶杀/武器
贩卖毒品  斗殴  持枪抢劫  威胁
Distro, agg assault, armed robbery, intimidation.
-他是打着谁的旗号  -没谁
- Whose flag does he fly? - Nobody's.
他是个独狼  从我了解的情况看
He's a lone wolf. From what I understand,
他雇佣没加入黑帮的孩子来卖毒品
he recruits unaffiliated kids to deal dope
并通过威胁老实的店老板来收保护费
and shake down good business owners for protection money.
-好吧  有人开口了吗  -还没有
- All right. Anybody talking? - No one so far.
但很明显披萨店的店主被骚扰了
But it's pretty clear that pizza guy is getting harassed
或者他看见了什么
or saw something.
他只是不想掺和进来
He just doesn't want to get involved.
我们还知道罗伊也被骚扰了
Well, we also know Roy was getting harassed.
组织犯罪技术部破解了他的电话
OCD Lab dumped his phone,
近一个月里有部一次性手机
and he's been getting threatening text messages
一直在给他发威胁短信
for about a month from a burner.
这些是最近的
These are the most recent.
两周前  上周  昨天
两周前  "时间不多了  老家伙"
Two weeks ago, "Tick tock, old man."
上周  "该掏钱了"
Last week, "Time to pay."
昨天  "我的枪已经拔出来了"
And yesterday, "My gun's untucked."
所有的短信都是在五金店附近
All the messages are coming within the vicinity
发出来的
of the hardware store.
罗伊被杀后  电话就关机了
And after Roy's murder, the phone was turned off.
听起来罗伊不想配合
Sounds like Roy didn't want to play the game,
昆西便决定拿他开刀
so Quincy decided to make an example out of him,
以儆效尤
send a message.
我们还有什么收获
All right, so what else we got?
我们排查时  一名目击者告诉我们
During our canvass, a witness told us
枪杀案件发生20分钟之前他们看见
that they saw a beige SUV patrolling the block
一辆米黄色越野车在这一带来回巡逻
for about 20 minutes before the shooting.
玻璃上贴了膜  我们做了功课
Had tinted windows. We did our homework.
昆西开一辆米黄色的凯雷德
Quincy drives a beige Escalade.
保安监控上有吗
Okay. We catch it on any security cams?
没有  他运气比较好
No, he got lucky.
看起来他的好运气刚刚用完了
Well, it looks like his luck just ran out.
我要调点东西出来
I'm gonna pull something up.
这是马路对面杰克逊大街上的
So this was captured on POD footage
一家洗车店的监控
across the streets from a car wash on Jackson
在罗伊被杀两小时后拍到的
two hours after Roy was killed.
那辆凯雷德登记在昆西·巴雷特名下
That Escalade's registered to Quincy Barrett.
而那家伙  看着像
And that guy, it looks like
在清理驾驶座
he's only cleaning the driver's side.
好  有谁认识他吗
All right. Anybody recognize him?
不认识  我觉得他看着不像昆西·巴雷特
No, he doesn't look like Quincy Barrett to me.
-太远了没法做面部识别  -对
- Too far for a facial rec. - Yeah.
好  我们先确认这位洗车人的身份
Okay, so let's ID this car washer.
我们得想办法进那辆凯雷德查查
We gotta figure out a way to get inside that Escalade.
只要在里面发现罗伊的血迹  案子就破了
You find Roy's blood in there, it's game over.
没看到凯雷德
No Escalade.
杰  我们都在后面准备好了
Hey, Jay, we're all set back here.
收到
Copy.
芝加哥警署  开门
Chicago PD. Open up.
里面的人刚刚把一把枪放进红色背包
Guy inside just dropped a gun into a red backpack.
-不是昆西  -伙计们  注意
- Not Quincy. - Guys, heads up.
里面的人刚刚藏起了一把枪  保持冷静
Guy inside just hid a gun. Stay frosty.
收到
Copy that.
昆西·巴雷特
Quincy Barrett.
什么事
The hell is this?
我们接到报警说你的车被用于肇事逃逸
We got a report that your car was used in a hit and run.
我们想看看你的车
We'd like to look at your vehicle.
行  祝你们好运吧
Yeah. Well, good luck with that.
-什么意思  -我的车被偷了
- What's that mean? - Someone stole it.
我不知道  也许是偷车的人
I don't know. Maybe whoever stole it
肇事逃逸了
did that hit and run.
-你报失了吗  -还没
- Did you report the theft? - Nah, not yet.
但你们知道吗  也许你们能帮我
But you know what? Maybe y'all can help me out.
去找车吧
You know, start looking.
你昨天下午在哪里  昆西
Where were you yesterday afternoon, Quincy?
你们都听到电话响了吧
Y'all hear that phone ringing?
是我律师的电话
That's my lawyer calling,
让我什么都不要说
telling me to keep my damn mouth shut.
祝你们愉快  警官们
Nice day, Officers.
海莉  我看到一位男性  黑人  20来岁
Hailey. Hey, I got a male, Black, 20s,
背着红色背包正要离开那栋房子
exiting the building with a red backpack.
好  就是他
Yeah, that's him.
包里可能有凶器  抓住他
Could be the murder weapon in there. Take him.
-收到  -哥们
- Copy that. - Hey, man.
芝加哥警署  我能跟你谈谈...
Chicago PD. Can I talk to you for--
慢着  慢着
Slow down. Slow down.
-我什么都没干  -好  手放下
- Yo, I haven't done anything. - Okay. Hands low.
手举起来
Hands high.
你为什么要跑
Why you running?
-我怕白人警察  -好  我是什么肤色
- White cops scare me. - Yeah. What color am I?
蓝色  也一样危险
Blue. Just as dangerous.
-包里有什么  哥们  -没什么
- What you got in here, man? - Nothing.
-没什么  是吗  -我知道你从昆西家出来
- Nothing, huh? - I know you leaving Quincy's.
你要干什么  又去洗车吗
What you doing? Washing cars again?
我不知道你在说什么  哥们
I don't know what you're talking about, man.
我们只是在打游戏
We were just playing video games.
凯文  没错  就是个游戏手柄
Kev, yeah. It's just a gaming controller.
我说了吧
Like I say.
能还给我吗
Can I have it back?
离车远点  你叫什么名字
Off the car. What's your name?
-达马里·埃文斯  -你有持枪许可证吗
- Damari Evans. - You got a license?
你昨天下午三点在哪里  为什么
Where were you yesterday at 3:00 P.M., and why?
米得威医院
Midway Hospital.
我弟弟癫痫发作
My little brother had a seizure.
-我能走了吗  -走吧
- Can I go now? - Go for it.
达马里  如果我发现你跟罗伊·希尔的谋杀
Damari, if I find out you had anything to do
有任何关系
with the murder of Roy Hill,
我们就会再见面  好吗
we'll see each other again, okay?
好  这是达马里·埃文斯和他弟弟西奥
Okay, so that's Damari Evans and his younger brother, Theo,
在米得威医院
at Midway Hospital.
就是罗伊·希尔被谋杀的那天
This is the same day that Roy Hill is murdered,
他们下午两点半到四点都在候诊室里
and they are in that waiting room from 2:30 to 4:00 P.M.
罗伊是几点中枪的
And what time was Roy shot?
枪击报警电话是3点15分打来的
Shots fired call came in at 3:15.
好  所以达马里只是帮他洗车
All right, so Damari's his cleaner,
-没帮他杀人  -这说明
- not his killer. - Which would suggest
-昆西自己干脏活  -好
- Quincy did his own dirty work. - All right.
我们找到这辆凯雷德了吗
Were we ever able to track down this Escalade?
没有  可能因为里面有太多血了
No. There's probably too much blood in there,
他把它藏起来了
and he's hidden it somewhere.
好  我们还有其他关于达马里的信息吗
All right. What else do we know about Damari?
有  他因贩毒被捕一次  因暴力袭警被捕两次
Yeah, he's got one bust for distro, two agg assaults.
他15岁就在帮派数据库里了
He's been in the gang database since he's 15,
他跟他弟弟西奥住在一起
and he lives with his little brother, Theo.
好  但西奥是位全优生
Okay, so Theo is a straight-A student,
只拿过一次良+
one B-plus.
他患有严重的癫痫
He has a severe form of epilepsy,
需要频繁就医
which requires a ton of medical attention,
而且他们的父母都不在
and both parents are out of the picture.
好  所以他身兼数职
Right, so he's the mother, father, brother,
-还要养家糊口  -对  这对我们有好处
- breadwinner wrapped in one. - Yeah, and that's good for us.
这意味着达马里很脆弱
It means Damari's vulnerable.
好  我们去找他
Right, we jam him up,
让他为了保护西奥而供出昆西
get him to flip on Quincy to protect Theo.
我们得装成大客户去找他
We need to come at him as a big-time buyer.
该怎么做
But how?
除了我  你们都暴露了
Besides me, you guys are all burned,
而且我很确定达马里不想卖货给我
and I'm pretty sure Damari doesn't want to sell to me.
-很高兴见到你  -好  再联系
- Good to see you. - All right. I'll catch you.
有什么需要吗  兄弟
What you need, homie?
不用
I'm good.
但有人跟着你
But you got company.
怎么说
How's that?
你看到街尾那辆灰色皮卡了吗
You see that gray pickup down the block?
看到了吗  里面那对男女
You see it? That man, woman?
比雪还白
Whiter than Christmas?
我赌一百他们是警察
I'll bet a hundo they police.
芝加哥警署  把手给我看
Chicago PD. Let me see your hands.
-喂  我们什么也没干  -手举起来
- Yo, we ain't do nothing. - Put your hands up.
闭嘴  转身  面向围栏
Shut up, turn around. Face the fence.
我们搜身前  你们有什么能让我们
Before we pat you down, you got anything on you
-抓你们的东西吗  -没有  警官
- that's gonna stick us? - No, I do not, Officer.
我只是在等我弟弟
I'm just waiting on my little brother.
老兄  你可以继续  我知道我的权利
Man, y'all can just keep on stepping. I know my rights.
别跟我说什么权力
Don't talk to me about rights.
我知道你在卖货  东西呢
I know you're selling, so where is it?
走开  你没权利骚扰
Back up, man. You ain't got no right to harass--
冷静
Calm down.
快逃
Come on!
他的这拳可不轻啊
He got you pretty good.
我让他假戏真做
I told him to make it look real,
但不是这么真
but not that real.
那我们该带你去医院吗
Should we take you to Med?
干得好  库珀
Good job, Coop.
通常需要好几天才能做成第一次买卖
It usually takes a few days before you land your first deal.
是啊  但一起从警察手下逃跑
Yeah, well, you know it ain't nothing like running from cops
最能加深兄弟情谊了  对吧
to bring brothers together, right?
如果我进了地下室  这东西还能传信号吗
This thing still transmit if I go into a basement?
-能  半英里半径都行  -我看看
- Yeah, half a mile radius. - Let me see.
-试试  -好了
- Let's see. - Here you go.
嗯
Okay.
达马里知道你什么
So what does Damari know about you?
我叫肖恩·希克斯  来自奥本公园
Name's Sean Hicks. From Auburn Park.
上了塔夫特高中
Went to Taft High School.
对了  他问了我塔夫特的吉祥物  你说得对
By the way, he tested me on the Taft mascot. You were right.
你跟他说了你生病的妈妈吗
You tell him about your sick mom?
没有
No.
没想到我得说这么深入
Didn't think I needed to take it that far.
感觉这有点利用隐私了
Felt like we were exploiting a private situation.
我们就要这么做
That's exactly what we're doing.
达马里有个生病的弟弟
Damari's got a sick brother.
他会欣赏你照顾生病的妈妈
He's gonna respect you for taking care of your sick mother.
得把所有相似点都利用起来
Gotta use any commonality we can find.
听着  记住任务  好吗
Look, stay on point, okay?
我们在监视  但不会太近
We're watching, but not too close.
而那条街的混混  都非常警惕
And the bangers on that block, they got their radar up.
感觉不妙就赶紧走人
You catch a bad vibe, you walk.
-懂了吗  -知道了  长官
- Right? - Yes, sir.
-好  -那跟我说说
- All right. - Well, talk to me, man.
你上的是什么高中
What high school did you go to?
博林布鲁克高中
I went to Bolingbrook High.
南边郊区  不错啊
South suburb. A'ight.
你就确保照顾好自己就行
You just make sure you take care of yourself in there.
别进去谈什么曲棍球或网球这种高级运动
Don't go in there talking about lacrosse or tennis.
这你不用担心
You don't have to worry about that.
为什么
Why is that?
我参加的是高尔夫球队
I was on the golf team.
我来抓你了  小子
Ooh, coming to get you, boy.
想得美
Don't think so.
尝尝碳爆炸机的威力吧
Taste the carbon blaster!
太冷血了
Oh, that's cold.
你想跟这小子打一把吗
Yo, you wanna take a run up against this punk?
不了  我不能久留
Nah, man, I can't stay too long.
得带我妈去医院
Gotta take Moms to the hospital.
怎么了
Yo, what happened?
她有癌症
She got cancer.
肺癌
In the lungs.
一周三次化疗
In chemo three times a week.
那太难了  哥们
Yo, that's tough, bro.
真遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
是啊  确实不好
Yeah, it ain't pretty.
也不便宜
Or cheap.
那你
So you...
一直都在付所有帐单吗
been holding down all the bills?
对  别无选择
Yeah. Ain't got no choice.
我懂你  兄弟
I hear you, bro.
你想买多少
So how much you looking to buy?
西奥  西奥
Theo. Theo!
西奥  来  侧身躺下
Theo, come on. Lay on your side for me.
西奥
Theo.
呼吸  呼吸
Just breathe. Just breathe.
这孩子犯癫痫了
The kid's seizing.
加油  呼吸
Come on, man. Just breathe.
-你在干什么  -叫救护车
- What the hell are you doing? - Calling an ambulance--
不  哥们  我有药
No, man! I got product here.
听着  他需要药
Look, he needs his medicine.
去我的房间  在衣柜上
Just go to my room. It's on the dresser.
我们得叫救护车
We're gonna have to call an ambo.
不不  先等等
No, no, no. Just give it a minute.
我不想暴露库珀
I don't want Cooper to get burned.
赶紧  库珀  快点  快点
Come on, Coop. Hurry up. Hurry up.
吸入  你能做到
Inhale, buddy. You can do it.
好了
Come on now.
呼吸  小西
Just breathe, T.
好了  呼吸
There you go. Breathe.
-你还好吗  -嗯
- You all right? - Good.
对  他会没事的
Yeah. He's gonna be fine.
-对吧  西奥  -对  我没事
- Right, Theo? - Yeah, I'm good.
抱歉  我不想吓你们的
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you guys.
反正是被你吓到了
Yeah, well, you did.
别再这样了  好吗
Yo, no more of that, okay?
太吓人了
It's scary as hell, man.
喂
Yo...
我们明天继续谈买卖的事
Yeah, we'll talk some more business tomorrow.
行
Yeah.
如果你需要什么就告诉我  说真的
Hit me up if you need anything. For real.
走了  小家伙
All right, little man.
昨晚在达马里家干得好
That was good work last night with Damari.
你保持了冷静
You kept your cool.
长官  我以为西奥要死了
Sir, I thought Theo was gonna die.
兄弟  我们不会让这种事发生
Hey, man, we would never let that happen.
-好  那就好  -喂
- Okay, good. Good to know. - Yeah...
听着  如果他病情没有马上稳定
Look, if things didn't stabilize quickly,
我们会介入  帮忙
we would've stepped in, helped out.
你确定是昆西·巴雷特吗
Are you sure it's Quincy Barrett?
鲍勃  把门锁上  待在后面  我们马上来  好吗
Bob, lock the door, stay in the back, and we'll check it out, okay?
好
All right.
是披萨店的鲍勃·海耶斯打来的
That was Bob Hayes from the pizza joint.
他说昆西在用银色凯美瑞车踩点
He says Quincy is casing it right now in a silver Camry.
我刚让海莉和杰去那边了
I got Hailey and Jay over there right now
跟进罗伊的凶杀案
doing follow-ups on Roy's murder.
你们过去  支援他们  我告诉他们
Head over there, back them up. I'll loop them in.
-去吧  -好
- Come on. - Okay.
我们知道昆西开一辆银色凯美瑞
We know Quincy was driving a silver Camry.
对
Yeah.
看起来里面没事
It looks okay inside.
凯文让他锁门了  对吧
Kev told him to lock up, right?
对
Yeah.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD.
芝加哥警署  举起手来
Whoa! Chicago PD! Get your hands up.
你是谁  你来这干什么
Who are you? What are you doing here?
我是特兰顿
I'm Trent.
我十秒前刚进来  拿披萨
I just came in 10 seconds ago to get a pizza.
门开着  我来找海耶斯先生的
The door was open. I'm looking for Mr. Hayes.
你有武器吗
Are you armed?
没有  我什么都没做  我只是来拿吃的
No! I didn't do anything. I just came to get some food.
-我保证  -好
- I promise. - Okay.
我要搜一下你的身  好吗
I'm just gonna search you for a second, all right?
好
Yeah.
没事  你看着他
All right. You got him?
好  我看着他
Yeah, I got him.
在这里待着  好吗
Hang out in that corner for a sec, okay?
有尸体
Body.
海莉  是鲍勃
Hailey, it's Bob.
5021G  发现一具尸体
5021 George, I got a bona fide DOA.
威尔逊路3433号
3433 Wilson Road.
海耶斯披萨店  让犯罪现场调查组来
Hayes' Pizza. Roll a crime lab.
收到  5021G
Copy that, 5021 George.
他胸口中了两枪  都是正中心
He took two to the chest, center mass.
脑袋上还挨了以前  以防万一
One insurance round to the face.
-收银机呢  -没动过
- Cash register? - Untouched.
那就是暗杀
All right, so it was a hit.
昆西知道他是目击证人  把他干掉了
Quincy knew he was a witness, tied it off.
听着  我们需要证据
All right, listen, we need evidence.
让人过来在附近调查
Let's get some boots on the ground now.
-赶紧  -没问题
- Come on. - You got it.
-库珀  -怎么了
- Coop. - Sir?
收到一条短息
Just got a text.
看起来达马里想见面谈买卖
Looks like Damari wants to meet up and do the deal.
好  去干吧
Okay, good. Let's get it done.
去告诉阿特沃特  他会帮你
Talk to Atwater. He'll set you up.
警长  你有时间吗
Sarge, you got a sec?
达马里会怎么样
What's gonna happen to Damari?
什么意思
What do you mean?
如果我们逮捕他
Say we arrest him.
他同意帮我们抓住昆西
He agrees to help us take out Quincy.
这能谈到什么条件
What kind of deal we talking?
取决于他帮了多少
Depends on how helpful he is
以及他在两起凶案中的角色
and how involved he was in the two murders.
如果他坐牢了  西奥会怎么样
If he does time, what happens to Theo?
儿童和家庭服务局可能会介入
DCFS will probably step in.
所以我们除掉了一个街头罪犯
So we take one criminal off the street
又制造了另一个
and just create another?
不确定这是个胜利
Not sure that's a victory.
好吧  听我说
All right, listen to me.
我们需要抓到昆西·巴雷特
We need to take down Quincy Barrett.
那是我们的重心
That's our focus.
那是任务
That's the job.
你来了
Yeah. There he is.
兄弟  你怎么样
Hey, man. How you doing?
-都好  -你妈妈怎么样了
- All good. - How's your mama?
她很好  谢谢询问
She's good, man. Thanks for asking.
她得了什么癌症来着
Yo, what kind of cancer she got again?
肺癌
Lung.
对  我阿姨也得了那个
Yeah, my aunt had that.
兄弟  你想过我们之前谈的
Yo, dawg, what you think about that investment idea
那个投资想法吗
we talked about earlier?
凯文  兄弟  你知道我一直支持你
Aw, Kev. Bro, you know I'm with you all the way,
但我不喜欢那主意
but I don't like that one.
你不喜欢
You don't like it?
我只是觉得那片社区没潜力
Well, I don't think that that neighborhood's on the up.
什么叫"没潜力"  所有东西都可以有潜力
What do you mean "on the up"? Anything can be on the up
只要在正确的时间  投入精力
if you get there at the right time and you put the work in.
所以  我搞到了
So...I was able to get
一百克  纯的
100 grams, uncut.
对
Yeah.
钱都在这了
It's all there.
酷  兄弟  那我们交易吧
Cool. Man, let's do it.
等等  等等
Yo, hold up. Hold up.
老天  真是没完了
Man, it never stops, bro.
-怎么了  -西奥的病
- What happened? - Theo's medical stuff.
他又犯癫痫了
He just had another seizure.
校长带他去急诊室了
Principal took him down to the ER.
真遗憾
Sorry to hear that.
不  没事  他们就是在巡逻
No, that's okay. They just cruising.
我去年花了一万三医药费
I spent 13 grand last year on medical bills.
-你能信吗  -见鬼
- Can you believe that? - Damn.
怪不得我得贩毒了  兄弟
No wonder why I gotta sell dope, man.
等等  等等
Yo, wait. Hold on. Hold on.
不如你去急诊室看西奥吧
How about you go to the ER to check on Theo?
我们晚上再交易
We'll do the deal later tonight.
不  搞什么
No. What the hell?
-别啊  库珀  -搞什么
- Come on, Coop. - What the hell?
不用  兄弟  没事  我们可以用袋子
Nah, man. It's cool. We can just bang it--
不  兄弟  那些警察让我紧张
Nah, man. These cops is making me nervous.
干嘛冒险  你懂我意思吗
Why risk? You know what I'm saying?
行  我们晚点见
Yeah, let's hook up later, man.
好  没问题
All right. Bet.
搞什么
What was that?
那算什么  你搞什么
What was that? What was that?
我们还有两分钟就能抓人了
We're two minutes away from making the arrest--
那边有一辆巡逻车
There was a patrol car out there.
如果我们被抓了
If we got harassed,
-如果他们要我的身份证  -安德烈
- if they asked for my license-- - Andre.
所以你退缩了
That's why you backstopped.
你的证件没问题  你的名字没案底
You got a clean license, you got a clean name,
就算他们想也无法暴露你
They couldn't blow your cover if they wanted to.
我就是感觉不对  好吧
Yo, it just didn't feel right, okay?
所以我那时做了决定
So I made a call in the moment.
但一切都好
But we still good.
我们今晚会交易
We're doing the deal later tonight.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
你这是什么意思
The hell does that mean?
他是说你得少担心达马里
That means you gotta worry less about Damari
多关心两个受害者的家庭
and more about the families of the two dead bodies.
罗伊·希尔  鲍勃·海耶斯
Roy Hill. Bob Hayes.
这份工作很难
This job is hard.
尤其是你想做正确的事时
Especially when you're trying to do right.
你在乎的越多  事情就变得更难
The more you care, it actually gets harder.
所以如果你做不到
So if this isn't something that you can do,
如果你觉得自己应付不了  就别干
if you don't think you can handle it, step aside.
但无论如何  我们有任务  而且要完成
But either way, we got jobs to do, and we gotta get it done.
那是他的决定  凯文
That was his call, Kevin.
是他在卧底
He was the one in play.
而且当时确实有巡逻车
And Patrol was in the vicinity.
好吧  那如果躲在楼里
Okay, well, how about just ducking in the building
继续交易呢
and keeping the deal going?
他是新手  还在学习
He's new. He's learning.
这我知道  但我觉得还有内情
I understand that, but I think there's more to it.
-你说  -他对达马里很心软
- Okay. - He got a very soft spot for Damari.
我们不能忘了上周发生的事
We can't forget about what just happened last week.
他看着自己的白人搭档杀了一个无辜的黑人
He watched his white partner kill an innocent Black man.
他有很多心事
He's got a lot on his mind,
这让我有点担心
and it's starting to worry me a little bit.
好  那你决定
Okay, you make the call.
你想把他撤下去吗
You want to pull him?
警长  凯文  有发现
Sarge, Kev, I got something.
我们发现昆西的信用卡在小超市用过
We picked off Quincy's credit card at a mini mart
就在鲍勃·海耶斯被枪杀二十分钟后
20 minutes after Bob Hayes got shot.
我们接入了他们的安保服务器
We tapped into their security server
能看到里面和外面的监控
for the camera inside and out.
他走进去  买了一包香烟
He walks in, buys a pack of cigarettes,
走出来  在停车场见了一个人
walks out, meets with someone in the parking lot.
看起来他把凶器给了达马里
Looks like he handed the murder weapon off to Damari.
我猜他的工作就是藏枪或处理枪
Guessing his job was to stash it or dump it.
问题是  在哪里
The question is, where?
-答案就在那部手机里  -对  你说得对
- And the answer is in that phone. - Yeah, you're right.
我们查到手机号码  就能找到枪
We ID that cell number, we find the gun.
那你觉得库珀能行吗
So, do you think Cooper can handle it?
好  告诉他进度
All right. Get him up to speed.
兄弟  你不用这么做
Yo, man. You ain't gotta do this.
没事  反正有剩的
Nah, I got plenty.
那小家伙  吃饭跟小鸡啄米一样
Ding-dong over there, he eats like a bird.
吃吧
Dig in.
这是我起码能做的
It's the least I could do.
你救了我两次  在两天之内
You saved me twice in, like, two days.
你就像个能嗅出警察的狗一样
You're like a cop-sniffing dog.
好吧  这是达马里在说笑
All right, is this Damari just playing,
还是他起疑心了
or he getting suspicious?
两天两次  频率不小
Twice in two days. That is a lot.
拜托
I mean, come on.
你觉得呢  警长
What do you think, Sarge?
我觉得是起疑心了
My vote is suspicious.
我们该让他出来了吗
Think we should pull him?
我们还没听到安全词
All right, we haven't heard the safe word yet.
先顺其自然
Let's let it play for now.
我眼神不错
Hey, I got good eyes.
耳朵也灵
Good ears too.
而且我也不喜欢警察
And I don't like police neither,
所以我总是很警惕他们在哪
so I'm always aware of where they are,
在骚扰谁  好让自己不被坑
who they harassing, so don't even trip.
是啊
Yeah, well,
这片社区有好多警察
there's plenty of them up in this neighborhood
吓大伙儿
sweating folks.
也总是想找麻烦
Always looking for problems too.
以前吧
Used to.
我得承认  现在事情有点不同了
I gotta admit, things are a little different now.
我知道这有点好笑  看着警察礼貌友善
I know it's kind of fun, watching cops act all polite and nice.
他们最近受了不少苦
Yo, they've been catching so much hell
连自己的影子都害怕
that they scared of their own shadows.
反正也是他们自作自受
It ain't like they don't deserve it.
我懂  兄弟  但是
I get you bro, but
我们也不是什么好货
it's not like we all choir boys.
我们有些人
You know, some of us
确实犯法了
actually do break the law.
你有厕所吗
Hey, uh, you got a bathroom I could use?
嗯  走廊尽头左边
Yeah, down the hall, to the left.
你在干什么  老兄
The hell you doing, man?
我本来想去厕所  后来看到了海报
I was going to the bathroom, I saw the poster.
这大概是他的第一张海报吧
Had to be dude's first poster he ever did.
我都没见过  不过  抱歉是我错了
I ain't ever seen it before. But you know, my bad, man.
-我无意...  -没事  没关系
- I ain't mean-- - Nah, man, it's all cool.
我也不是那么紧张的人
I ain't uptight like that.
那就好
Cool.
带上外套  我们得走了
Yo, grab your coat, man. We need to bounce.
我们要去哪
Where we going?
去见昆西
Meet up with Quincy.
库珀
Yo, Coop.
我们不是说过这个吗
Didn't we talk about this?
别离开  兄弟
Do not travel, dawg.
怎么了
What's wrong?
只是  你没说过我们要见
It's just, you didn't tell me we was meeting up
-你的老大  -对  但他刚发信息了
- with big boss man. - Yeah, he just texted.
你带钱了吗
You bring the cash?
带了  在我外套里
Yeah. It's in my coat.
那就行  走吧
All right. Come on.
怎么了
Yo, what's the matter?
你不信任我吗
You don't trust me?
我当然信任你  兄弟
Of course I trust you, man.
当他们开始问你信不信任他们时
When they start asking if you trust them--
就说明他们不信任你了
Then they don't trust you.
还有一件事
One more thing.
不能带手机
No cell phones.
警长  我们要让他们出去吗
Hey, Sarge, are we really gonna let them go mobile?
我们没有选择
We don't really have a choice.
收到
Copy that.
嗯  收到
All right, 10-4.
警长  他们要进达马里的车了
Sarge, they're getting in Damari's car.
把钱放在车座下
Yo, stuff the cash under the seat.
以防我们被拦下
In case we get stopped.
老天  你真是新手
Man, you is raw.
我们要去哪
Man, where are we going?
别问这么多问题了  兄弟
Yo, stop asking so many questions, bro.
放松
Just chill.
拜托  老兄  怎么回事
Come on, man. What's going on?
走开  走开
Move on. Move on.
-不是吧  -你得让他走
- Come on. - Bro, you gotta get him.
开玩笑吗  怎么回事
Is this a joke? What the hell, man?
快去
Come on, bro.
警长  我们被一辆垃圾车堵住了
Hey, Sarge, we getting blocked by a garbage truck.
你能看到吗
You got eyes?
-不行  -我上报找后援
- That's a negative. - I'll call it in.
把车开走  赶紧开走
Get this truck out of here. Get out of here!
我们要失去信号了  凯文
We're losing the feed, Kev.
好吧  我们启动手机定位
All right, we'll anticipate Cicero.
或许他们能收到
Maybe they're getting on the 290.
-好  车开走了  -你准备好了吗
- All right, here we go. - You ready?
-嗯  -好  我们走
- Yeah. - All right. Let's go.
-拜托  拜托  -我失去信号了
- Come on. Come on. Come on. - I lost signal.
那他得靠自己了
Well, he's on his own now.
-这孩子得靠自己了  -对
- This kid's on his own. - Yeah. Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's do this.
没消息吗  什么都没有
We got nothing? Nothing at all?
什么都没有  我们每五分钟
We got nothing. We got the BOLO going out
就发布一次通告  但一无所获
every five minutes. We got nothing.
-我  我不明白了  -我们说了不能移动
- I just--I don't understand. - We told him not to travel.
我们不是说了不能移动吗
Didn't we tell him not to travel?
-我知道  -拜托
- I know! - Come on, man!
我们得找到他  我们会找到的
We're gonna find him. We'll find him.
见鬼  忘了拿钱
Damn! Forgot the bread.
欢迎来到安吉星紧急服务
Welcome to OnStar Emergency.
-我的错  -没事
- My bad. - All good.
这事很常见吗
So this a normal thing?
他想见跟你做买卖的人
Him wanting to meet up with the people you do business with?
算不上"常见"  但是
I wouldn't say "Normal," but
他说了算
he calls the shots.
所以他说要见面  我们就见面
So when he says meet, we meet.
就这么简单
It's the way it is.
那里有货吗
Product in there?
当然
Yeah.
别担心
Don't worry.
会没事的
It's gonna be fine.
这里绝对没有警察
Definitely no cops in here.
是有点吓人  对吧
Man, it kind of spooky, ain't it?
是啊
Yeah.
好像是个
It feels like a place
拍恐怖电影的地方
where one of them horror movies take place.
你跟我正享点乐子  突然"砰"的一声
You and me having fun, then boom.
穿着小丑衣服的疯子出现
Crazy dude in a clown suit show up.
是啊  还带着锁链
Yeah, with a chainsaw.
好吧  这孩子在哪
Okay. Where is this kid?
芝加哥各巡逻队
Units on the Citywide.
我们收到了汽车的紧急呼救信号
We're getting a vehicle SOS distress signal.
多次尝试联系车主未果
Multiple attempts have been made to contact the occupants.
有人有空去贝尔蒙特北街420号吗
Anyone available to roll over to 420 North Belmont?
-去检查一下  -这里是2322号
- Check it out? - 2322.
我们过去看
We'll roll on that job.
是什么车
What kind of car are we looking at?
黑色别克君越  四门
Black Buick LaCrosse. Four-door.
伊利诺伊州车牌  W7Y527
Illinois plate. William-7-Young-527.
-那是库珀  我们走  -聪明
- That's Coop. Let's go. - Smart move.
那意味着他有危险了  赶紧
Okay, that means he's in trouble. Hey, hey, hey.
这里是5021  总部  那是我们通缉的车
5021. Squad, that's our BOLO vehicle.
我们过去看
We're rolling on it.
5021D  收到
5021 David, 10-4.
再干几年  我就收手
A few more years, man, and I'm done.
我就有足够的钱洗白自己
I'll have enough money to go legit.
做那个我之前跟你说的买卖
Start that business I was telling you about.
嗯
Yeah.
我还要做大
I'm gonna make it big too.
我要在郊区买一栋大房子
I'll buy one of those mansions in the suburbs.
知道吗  在湖边
You know, on the lake?
知道  听着很不错
Yeah, man. Sounds good to me.
我们可以去滑水
And we'll go water skiing.
在烤架上拷牛排
Then we'll cook steaks on the grill.
天呐
Man--
抱歉我迟到了  兄弟们
Sorry I'm late, fellas.
别担心
Oh, no worries.
这就是你跟我说的那小子
Ah, so this the dude you been telling me about.
对  肖恩
Yeah. Sean.
你是哪里人  肖恩
Where you from, Sean?
南区
South Side.
冬季公园公寓大楼
Winter Park Apartment Complex.
-18街和伍德布里奇  -不错
- 18th and Woodbridge. - Cool.
你跟谁住在那
Who you stay with over there?
我现在不住在那了  有自己的地方了
I don't stay there now. Got my own spot.
33街
33rd Street.
自己住很爽吧
Uh-huh, don't it feel good to be on your own?
独立
Independent?
说到这个
Speaking of which,
你加入了什么我该知道的帮派吗
you got any affiliations I need to know about?
我没加入帮派  兄弟
I ain't linked up with nobody, man.
一直独来独往
I always did my own thing.
那告诉我  小兄弟
So tell me, young brother,
你怎么认识达马里的
how'd you meet my man, Damari, again?
这个说起来有趣
It's kind of funny, actually.
我在国王大街走路
Was walking down King Street.
看到一个白人  还有一个女士  白人女士
Saw this white dude, this lady--white lady--
坐在这里  看起来漫不经心
sitting in the car acting all nonchalant.
然后我看到了达马里在街角
And I saw my man, Damari, on the corner.
想着他可能是在卖货
Figured he might be doing some business,
你懂吗
you know?
所以我就去提醒他  说他们可能是警察
So I gave him the heads-up. Thought they might be cops.
而且他们真的是
Sure enough, they were.
发现得及时啊
That's a good break.
对
Yeah.
他救了我免于牢狱之灾
He saved me in a pinch.
然后你们就成了  成了挚友吗
Then y'all became, like-- like best friends?
这倒说不上  但是
I don't know about all that, but
我们关系不错
we cool.
就开始谈做些买卖的事
Start talking about doing some business.
这很像那种电影
You know it's--it's kind of like one of them movies.
对吧  一个可爱的白人女孩
Right? You know, where the cute white chick
撞到了一个大帅哥
bump into the handsome dude?
他把咖啡洒了一身
He spilled coffee all over his dumb ass?
他们管这个叫  缘分
You know, they call that, um, serendipity.
对  就像巧合
Yeah, like a coincidence.
但是  问题是  肖恩
But, you know, the thing is, Sean, um,
我不相信缘分
I don't believe in serendipity.
缘分这东西
You know, serendipity, it--
说不好  让我紧张的很
I don't know, it make me nervous as hell.
不  昆  老兄  你搞错了
Nah, Q. Man, you got it wrong--
我没跟你说话  小子
I ain't talking to you, boy.
那你是什么情况
No, so what is it about you?
怎么  想洗清自己的案底  你在帮警察
What? You working off a case? You helping out police? Like--
-不是那样的  -我跟你说了
- It ain't like that-- - Yo, I told you,
-你给我闭嘴  -没事
- keep your mouth shut! - It's cool.
没事
It's cool.
我知道你为什么会这么想
I understand where you're coming from.
我从没被警察抓过
I ain't never been arrested.
所以我也没什么需要洗清的案底
So I ain't got no case to work off.
昆  他没事  兄弟
Yo, Q. He's straight, man.
都没事  这不是你想的那样
It's all cool. It's not what you think it is, man--
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
放下
Drop the--
安德烈  你还好吗  你受伤了吗
Andre, are you good? You hit?
-我没事  -上报
- Yeah, I'm good. - Call it in.
贝尔蒙特北街420号
420 North Belmont.
总部  有人中枪
Squad, man shot!
贝尔蒙特北街420号需要救护车
I need a ambo at 420 North Belmont!
收到  救护车马上到
Copy that. Ambo on the way.
挺住  达马里  坚持住
Come on, Damari. Hang on, man.
为了西奥挺住
Stay strong for Theo.
你是...
You're...
你是警察吗
you're a cop?
挺住  兄弟
Hang on, man.
-挺住  挺住  -你是警察
- Just hang on. Hang on. - You're a cop.
挺住
Hang on.
别跑了
Stop running!
别动
Stop moving!
站住  别动
Stop! Moving!
枪缴械了
Gun's clear.
昆西·巴雷特  你被捕了
Quincy Barrett, you're under arrest.
起来
Get up.
你还好吗
You okay?
有达马里的消息吗
Any word on Damari?
有
Yeah.
他死了
He's dead.
这不是你的错
It's not on you.
一点也不是
Not even a little bit.
他生活不易  我懂
He had a hard life. I get that.
但决定替昆西卖命
But it was his decision to work for Quincy,
卖毒品
to sell drugs,
恐吓老实本分的生意人  掩盖谋杀
to shake down honest business owners, and cover up murders.
如果你选择了那种生活
I mean, when you sign up for that life,
死就成了其中的一部分
dying's a part of the game.
你说教完了吗
You done preaching?
别这样
Don't do that.
我没在说教
I'm not preaching.
我只是告诉你实际情况
I'm just telling you exactly what it is.
这不是《蝙蝠侠》  兄弟
This ain't "Batman," Dawg.
罪犯不戴面具  他们不是疯子
The criminals don't wear masks. They don't act all crazy.
有些人很聪明  有魅力
Some of them are smart, and they're charming.
他们会照顾自己的母亲  父亲
They take care of their mothers, and their fathers,
叔叔
and their uncles.
还有他们的弟弟
And their little brothers too.
这些我都懂
You know, I get that.
但我感觉我们能做得更好些
But I feel like we could've done better.
我觉得我们能告诉达马里内情
I feel like we could've told Damari what was going on
最好的是他能配合
and best thing, he'll cooperate.
我们可以照顾西奥
We could've took care of Theo.
肯定还有更好的方法
There's gotta be a better way to do this
不用白白牺牲无辜的黑人性命
without destroying innocent Black lives.
我只是这个意思
That's all I'm saying.
我们必须要用上达马里
I mean, we had to put Damari into play
才能为罗伊·希尔和鲍勃·海耶斯伸张正义
to get justice for Roy Hills and Bob Hayes.
他们也是无辜的黑人性命
Innocent Black lives.
这个问题没有简单明了的答案
There's not a easy answer to this problem.
但我们在这  已经是在解决问题了
But us being here is part of the solution.